NGUYEN HOANG MINH THO

Administration Staff - Receptionist



minhthohoang.work@gmail.com

**** 0975264940

Obstrict 10, HCMC

SUMMARY

Bachelor's degree in International Business with nearly one year of experience in operations and related fields. Experienced in sourcing efficient vendors, placing orders, handling deliveries, and processing payment documents. Proficient in managing and storing documents, photocopying, sending and receiving mail, supporting events, managing meeting rooms, and performing other administrative tasks

EDUCATION

Ho Chi Minh City University of Foreign Languages and Information Technology – HUFLIT

2020 - 2024

International Business

With Outstanding advantages:

- Secretary ranked Good for 4 years
- Student Policy Scholarship (2020-2021, 2022-2023); KEB HANA Scholarship (2022); Thanh Son Scholarship (2024)

SKILLS

Microsoft Office; Basic English Communication; Problem-Solving; Learning Spirit and Work Responsibility; Work Independently and Proactively; Work Under High Pressures; Teamwork Spirit; Time Management and Organization; Willing To Work Overtime

WORK EXPERIENCE

GS25 VIET NAM

08/2024 - 12/2024

Procurement Executive

Supported in arranging meetings with partners, scheduled meetings for the manager, and met new suppliers directly to offer products

Received and processed purchase requests from departments (MD, I&C department)

Sourced new suppliers, requested quotations and compared prices

Negotiated (pricing, materials, payment terms) and proposed suitable suppliers

Placed orders and coordinated with other departments to ensure compliance with procurement procedures and contract terms (based on project requirements)

Monitored payment progress, contract deadlines and built relationships with suppliers

CENTRAL RETAIL

08/2023 - 1/2024

Operation Intern

Made payment records for suppliers, utilities, business trip expenses,... of the supermarket Monitored employee business travel schedules, handled borrowed taxi cards, processed travel allowance claims

Coordinated with the accounting department to adjust payment-related documents Managed and stored documentation (payment records, contracts, POs, documents)

Sent/Received mail from suppliers and supermarkets

Regularly monitored outstanding debts and contract deadlines to ensure smooth operations Supported in checking office supplies and equipment for the office and supermarket monthly orders

Supported in organizing team events such as birthdays, anniversaries,...

CT LOGISTICS

05/2023 - 07/2023

Documentation Intern

Learning knowledge of export documentation processes and customer requirements Prepared Booking Note, HBL, MBL, and invoices under direct guidance

CERTIFICATE

06/2023

Microsoft Office Specialist (MOS)

06/2023 TOEIC 605 (LR)